appliancesconnection.com 2013-12-03

# Privacy Policy | AppliancesConnection.com

* * *

Effective Date April 18th, 2012

Your privacy is important to AppliancesConnection on the website www.appliancesconnection.com. We understand that all information transferred on our website is private and sensitive. Listed below is how we protect our customers from online fraud and protect your personal information. Let us know if you have any questions that are not covered on this page.

**Information That We Collect**

We collect the following personal information from you

* Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
* Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
* Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
* Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

**We Use this information to... **

* Fulfill your order
* Send you an order confirmation
* Send you requested product or service information
* Send product updates or warranty information
* Respond to customer service requests
* Administer your account
* Send you a newsletter
* Send you marketing communications
* Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
* Respond to your questions and concerns

Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at unsubscribe@AppliancesConnection.com. 

**Data Sharing **

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.  AppliancesConnection does not provide any third party with any individually identifiable information other than that which is necessary to complete your order.  AppliancesConnection has strict guidelines requiring all third parties to keep any shared personal information confidential. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

Service Providers  
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. Specifically, AppliancesConnection gives your name, shipping address, phone number, and order information to our shipping carrier. AppliancesConnection also provides your name, billing address, and credit card information to the credit card processor who bills your account. 

Legal Disclaimer  
We may also disclose your personal information:

* as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 
* when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
* to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 
* if AppliancesConnection is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
* to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

**User Access and Choice**

If your personally information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed from a product testimonial on our site by making the change on our account information page or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

 **Tracking Technologies / Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. For more information on cookies, please read the following [article at WikiPedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).

[ _Explain how cookies are used on your_ _website._ ] Cookies are used on our site to keep track of the referring website, your recent history and to maintain any items that are placed in your shopping cart for your convenience. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.  Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

 **Web Beacons / Gifs**

We employ [or our third party advertising partner employs] a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. The clear gifs used on this site are used to report order total and item sales for tallying.

Safe Shopping Guarantee

We guarantee that every online transaction you make will be 100% safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at AppliancesConnection.Com. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, we will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card issuer in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

Transactional Information

We make every effort to ensure that your purchase experience at AppliancesConnection.Com is secure. We use state-of-the-art data encryption technology to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your user information. Secure Socket Layers (SSLs) encrypt the information sent between your computer and our database. In addition, we use Internet fraud screening to protect credit card transactions. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

To be sure you're browsing secure pages, check your web browser status bar (located at the bottom of the window) for the closed padlock icon. This icon appears in the latest versions of Internet Explorer and Firefix to tell you that you are viewing a secure web page. Also, all browsers display an "s" after the "http" (https://�) in the website address to indicate that you're in a secure environment.

We also protect your purchase by preventing the shipment of merchandise to a fraudulent address. All billing addresses are verified electronically and all alternate shipping addresses are verified manually. Any customer shipping to an address that differs from the billing address must put this alternate address on file with his or her credit card company. We then call the credit card issuer to verify that the customer has indeed put the information on file.

**

Third Party Sites 

**

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of AppliancesConnection. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. **

Product Testimonials 

**

Our website also offers publicly accessible product testimonials. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from the product testimonial please contact us at.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Tell-a-Friend **

If you choose to tell a friend about a product, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting them to look at the product.  AppliancesConnection does not store this information and is only used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. Your friend may contact us at [info@AppliancesConnection.com](mailto:info@AppliancesConnection.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

 **Social Media and Widgets**

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. **

Updates to the Privacy Policy

**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will send a notification to the email address specified on the account or post a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you have a question that isn't answered here, please contact us and we'll be happy to answer it for you. You can e-mail us at [info@AppliancesConnection.com](mailto:info@AppliancesConnection.com) , or call our Customer Service department at 1-800-299-9470. Additionally, you can mail us at the below address. 

AppliancesConnection.com  
101-01 Foster Ave.  
Section A  
Brooklyn, NY 11236
